# **Bradley Benedict**

MyPortfolio.io BradBenedict200@gmail.com 603-845-9940

## **Summary**

I have worked in the resturant industry for the past five years and am ready for a career change. I am searching for a web development position after my time spent self-learning. I am confident in my HTML, CSS, and Javascript skills, along with using React.js and SCSS. I am a highly motivated indivdual and a quick learner. My ideal job would be a role where I can continue my learning and sharpen my development skills.

#### Skills

#### **Customer service**

Years of working directly with customers, both in person and on the phone, have sharpened my skills with people interaction. I am very comfortable talking to customers or clients, aswell as effectivly communicating with my co-workers. I think this is an essential skill as a developer because it allows me to work well with manangers, mentors, designers, and other developers.

#### Creative problem solving

Being a good server means being able to make sure multiple tables of people are happy, all at the same time. This gave me a great oppurtunity to work on my problem solving skills in a very fast paced eviornment. This has directly translated to my efforts to learn web development because I able to take a breath, step back for a moment, and calmly figure out a solution to whatever issue I am faced with in my code.

## Time mangement

Another important aspect to serving is being able to manage your time, and how you spend it while on the floor. Being able to figure out in what order and when you should grab drinks, ring in an order, greet your new table, and help the customer that's been eye-balling you is not easy. Knowing how fast you can complete each task is the best way to manage this situation. This has helped me structure how I approach my development and pace myself so I don't get overwhelmed. It allows me to look at the entire project and figure out where most of my time should be spent.

Work Experience	References
-----------------	------------

Woody's woodfired pizza	Rachel Ferrara
Golden, CO March 2021 - Current	603-657-0034
T-Bones Great American Eatery	Erick Shea
Derry, NH March 2020 - December 2020	603-706-0727
Red Robin	Paul Gallos
Manchester, NH April 2019 - March 2020	603-203-5121

#### **Education**

# **Manchester Community College**

Manchester, NH

#### **Londonderry High School**

Londonderry, NH